http://www.apuldramroses.co.uk/pages/privacy-policy

This site uses cookies to give you the best experience. Privacy Policy.
Privacy Policy
APULDRAM ROSES PRIVACY POLICYApuldram Roses ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”),together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to in this Privacy Policy, sets out the basis on which any personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”) we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your Personal Data and how we will treat it in respect of your use of apuldramroses.co.uk (“Our Site”).By using this website, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy. In the event of a conflict between the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of use, the Terms of use will prevail.Our details For the purposes of our business we are the data controller.  In respect of processing that we undertake on behalf of our clients we are the data processor and our client is the data controller who determines the purpose and means of the processing of personal data which they provide us with. There may be instances where we are a joint data controller with our client. Our data protection officer is Elizabeth Sawday and can be reached at esawday@apuldramroses.co.uk  How we use your information The following sections set out why we are processing your information, what information we collect, the legal basis for and duration of our processing of your information and (if applicable) who your information will be shared with and where those recipients are based. Which information do we process and for what purpose?We process the following information from you: Information you give us. Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.apuldramroses.co.uk (our site). This includes information you provide when you register to use our site, make an order, request marketing information, enter a competition, promotion or survey and when you report a problem with our site. The information you give us may include your name, address, company name, email address and phone number. Details of Your Visit to our Website. We collect non-personally identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available. This includes, but is not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and records of how you navigate the pages on our site and how you interact with the pages. IP addresses. We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. We process information you give us and that we collect about you for the following purposes: To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us. To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so. To notify you about changes to our service. What are the grounds for processing your information?We are processing your data on the following ground(s): you have previously given your consent to us processing your data the purposes stated in section 2.2, above; and/or the processing is necessary for achieving our legitimate interest in respect of the goods or services you have requested or purchased. In accordance with data protection law, we have carefully weighed your interests and fundamental rights and freedoms against our interest to process your information and are satisfied that we are justified in processing your information for this purpose. Duration and further processingWe will regularly review the personal data which we are holding about you, and will delete it as appropriate. We will store your personal data for no longer than is necessary for us to fulfil the purpose for which it was obtained and given consent for provided that we have a reasonable commercial case for doing so. To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements. Who is your information shared with?In order to achieve the purpose(s) set out in section 2.2 above, we will share your data only with the following people or group of people: our delivery partners where necessary to complete an order. (See section 2.10 for specific privacy policies of our third party providers) Subject to paragraph 2.6, we will never sell, share, or rent your personal data without your prior consent. It should be noted that, because we do not control the privacy practices of third parties, we advise that you read and fully understand their privacy policies in addition to this privacy policy. We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers’ wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience. We may disclose your personal information to third parties: In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets. If Apuldram Roses or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets. If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use or terms and conditions of supply and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Apuldram Roses, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  5. Access to informationYou have the right to access information held about you by making a written request to us. You must send us proof of your identity, or proof of authority if making the request on behalf of someone else, before we can supply the information to you. Requests should be sent to esawday@apuldramroses.co.uk. In certain circumstances, you will be entitled to receive the information in a structured, commonly used and machine readable form. We will be allowed to charge you for our reasonable administrative costs in collating and providing you with details of the requested information which we hold about you, if your request is clearly unfounded or excessive.  6. Changes to our privacy policyAny changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy. 7. ComplaintsYou have the general right to complain to us (in the first instance) and to the Information Commissioner's Office (if you are not satisfied by our response) if you have any concerns about how we hold and process your information. Our contact details are set out in section 8, below. The Information Commissioner's Office website is www.ico.org.uk. 8. ContactQuestions, comments and requests, including any complaints, regarding us or this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to esawday@apuldramroses.co.uk
